lol-mmr.com 2017-11-13

# Privacy Policy - LoL-MMR Blog

### Effective Date: February 23, 2016.

This Website, www.lol-mmr.com (hereinafter referred to as the “Website” or “Site”) is managed by Arctivate Development of Naykani Company (hereinafter referred to as “Arctivate”, “us”, “we”, or “our”). This page sets out the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy upon which you (means an individual who visits or uses the Website, hereinafter referred to as “User”, “you” or “your”) may make use of our services and Site. Please read these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy carefully before you start to use the Website.

### 1\. RIOT GAMES

1.1 The Website isn’t endorsed by Riot Games and doesn’t reflect the views or opinions of Riot Games (hereafter referred to as “Riot Games”) or anyone officially involved in producing or managing League of Legends. League of Legends and Riot Games are trademarks or registered trademarks of Riot Games, Inc. League of Legends © Riot Games, Inc.  
1.2 Use of Riot Games League of Legends intellectual property in this Website is expressly permitted by Riot Games and we utilise the Riot Games “Riot API”, complying with Riot Games “API Terms”, League of Legends End User License Agreement, Terms of Use, and Privacy Policy. We encourage you to likewise, consult and abide the terms, agreement and privacy notices mentioned.

## 2\. TERMS OF USE

The Website provides a free League of Legends fan based service for the user. By using the Site, you indicate that you accept these Terms of Use and that you agree to abide by them.

2.1 By continuing to use the Site you further agree to not use this Site, content and services contained herein for illegal purposes or any activity that may provoke termination of our rights by Riot Games. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, please refrain from using this Site.

2.2 Arctivate reserves the right to modify these Terms of Use at any time and will publish notifications of material modifications in our sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately when we post them and apply to all access to and use of the Site thereafter.

2.3 If the Terms of Use is updated, we will update the Effective Date at the top of the Terms of Use. By continuing to access the Website after notice of such modifications have been published, you signify your agreement to be bound by them. You are expected to check this page from time to time so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you.

2.4 Arctivate reserves the right to delete or alter the Website, any content and services contained therein. 2.5 All content in this Website, is the property of Arctivate unless indicated otherwise. By continuing to use the site you acknowledge that such material is protected by the laws of Brunei Darussalam and any other applicable international intellectual property legislation.

## 3\. PRIVACY POLICY

We only store data that is necessary, available and as permitted by Riot Games to enable the services we provide and to improve our Site and your user experience and interface. This policy explains how we collect, store and use your personal information while using the Website. By accepting our Privacy Policy when using the Website you indicate your consent to the use of your personal data in a manner described in this policy. Please read carefully our Privacy Policy to understand what we do with your personal information.

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time as with our site updates and will publish notifications of material modifications in our sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately when we post them and apply to all access to and use of the Website thereafter. If the policy is updated, we will update the Effective Date at the top of the policy. Your continued use of the Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates.

### 3.1 Data Privacy

If you are only browsing this Site, we do not capture data that allows us to identify you individually with exception of third party services that we outline in this page.

### 3.2 Secure Network

To safeguard your personal data, all electronic storage and transmission of personal data are secured with appropriate security technologies.

### 3.3 Google Analytics

The Site uses Google Analytics (“Google”) to collect visitor data and analyse traffic on our site. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. This information helps us understand customer interests and helps us improve our Site. When you visit our Site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used.

This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our Website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Website.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better Website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

Arctivate does not sell, give, or trade the statistics they store to any third parties for data-mining or marketing purposes.

Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of our Site, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

### 3.4 Google Adsense

Google adsense uses [DoubleClick](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090) in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

### 3.5 Links to Other Websites and Advertisements

Our Website may contain links to other Websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other Website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the Website in question.

## 4\. Availability of the Website

Arctivate accepts no liability for any disruption or non-availability of the Website resulting from external causes including, but not limited to, ISP equipment failure, host equipment failure, communications network failure, power failure, natural events, acts of war or legal restrictions and censorship.

## 5\. Disclaimer

All of the content contained on the Site is edited, checked, and verified for accuracy as much as it is possible to do so. However, we cannot guarantee either its accuracy or the safety of any external links it might contain. The Site, as well as its owners, affiliates, and contributing authors can therefore not be held responsible for any problems or damage that occurs as a result of making use of material contained on our site. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you can contact us through any of the available methods on our Site.
